Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 13.11.23 13:47:09
我叫Oliver Queen
My name is Oliver Queen.
经过岛上的五年炼狱生活
After five years on a hellish island,
我回家只有一个目的
拯救我的城市
I have come home with only
one goal-- to save my city.
我不能再像以前一样成为杀手
But to do so,I can't be
the killer I once was.
为祭奠我的朋友 我必须扮成某人
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
我必须掩盖身份
I must be something else.
绿箭侠 前情提要
尽管我很想让这个城市变得更安全
Previously on "Arrow"... As much as
I would love to make this city safer,
我的首要职责
是保住Queen集团 你也是
my first obligation is to Queen
Consolidated and yours is,too.
我仔细调查了Lawton
I did some reading up on Lawton.
- Lyla 听着
- 你以为我不知道是他杀了你弟弟吗
Lyla,listen-- Did you really think I
wouldn't find out that he killed your brother?
你在利用我
That you were using me?
他必须死
I need to see this guy in a bag.
你应该比其他任何人都懂
You,of all people,should get that.
好久不见
尤其是黑手党首领 Queen先生
Long time particularly for
Bratva captain.Mr.Queen.
- Anatoly Knyazev 他对你评价很高
- 必须的
Anatoly Knyazev, he speaks
very highly of you.He should.
我救过他
I saved his life.
你应该在上次董事会上
就签了这份报告的
You were supposed to sign this
report at last night's board meeting.
知道为什么没签吗
You know why you didn't?
也许是因为上次会议我没参加
Probably because I didn't attend
last night's board meeting.
那你在哪
Where were you?
除了这个公司之外我还有别的业务
I have other interests
outside of this company.
我没有
I don't.
Queen先生 你说我们是合伙人
我以为你是认真的
Mr.Queen-- I thought you were serious
when you said we were partners.
Isabel 我只不过没参加一次会议
Isabel,I missed one meeting.
那是这周 上周还有两次
This week.Last week,it was two meetings.
Queen先生
Mr.Queen.
自从我们接管后 公司收入急速增长
Companywide revenue is at double
digits since you and I took over.
- Oliver
- 什么事
- Oliver!
- Yes?
抱歉打扰你们了
I'm sorry to interrupt your... Grr!
我需要跟你说下今晚的安排
Um,I need to talk to you about
your plans for this evening.
和Harper先生的
With Mr.Harper?
我得走了
You'll have to excuse me.
我们还有活要干 这很重要
We have work to do.It's important.
我今晚的安排也很重要
So are my evening plans.
失陪
I'm sorry.
我们得给你想点高明的借口
We are going to have
to work on your excuses.
没错
You're right.
你应该多加防备
You should be more careful.
你现在完全暴露在外
You're completely exposed.
我知道你在
I knew you were there.
你要我告诉你
贩卖假钞的人什么时候行动
What,you wanted me to tell you when the
funny money guys were ready to make a sale?
我们现在可以开始了
Here we go.
没有我们 你回家
Not "we." Go home.
我有帮手
I already have help.
这是假货
Here's the fake.
再看看真货
Let's see the real.
你右上方有两个
You got two right above you.
六点钟方向还有一个
Another at your six.
住手 别动
Stay where you are,don't move!
我在执行公民逮捕
I want to make a citizen's arrest.
别动
Don't move.
完事了 我撤了
That's it.I'm clear.
X特遣队呼叫知更鸟
Task force X to Mockingbird.
目标到手 我们回来了
We have the prize,we're coming home.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly
Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 禾希饭 DB CXRR 金万藏 佐佐木 Crystal
校对: Andrea∞Quinn
时间轴:YTET-可可与可心 pluto无肉筋
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-可可与可心 pluto无肉筋
绿箭侠
第二季 第六集
Arrow
Season 2 Episode 06
你们是谁
Who are you people?
国家安全局 情报局
NSA?CIA?
我是Amanda Waller
My name is Amanda Waller.
我以为你们做事会精细点
I thought you A.R.G.U.S.guys
were supposed to be more subtle.
对我们来说算精细了
For us,this was subtle.
我要见Lyla Michaels
Then I want to see Lyla Michaels.
我也想
So do I.
Michaels特工已经不知去向
Agent Michaels has gone dark.
Lyla失踪了吗
Lyla's missing?
怎么回事
What happened?
她去莫斯科查一个线索
She was running down a lead in Moscow.
她已经缺席了两次日常电话报告
She's missed two of
her scheduled call-ins.
那你们打算怎么办
Well,what are you doing about it?
找你谈话
Speaking to you.
即使我们知道Lyla具体在俄罗斯哪
Even if we knew where in Russia Lyla is,
我的上级也会认为再派出一支部队
my superiors believe
sending in an extraction team
会引起国际纠纷
could cause an international incident.
对他们来说 Lyla已经死了
As far as they're concerned, she's
already a framed picture on our lobby wall.
为什么告诉我这些
Why are you telling me all this?
因为我知道你和Oliver Queen
每天晚上在忙些什么
Because I know how you and
Oliver Queen spend your nights.
我也知道你的护照还没过期
And I know your passport is up to date.
那你告诉我Lyla去莫斯科干什么
It would help to start with what Lyla
was doing in Moscow in the first place.
她要找什么线索
What was this lead
she was tracking down?
Floyd Lawton的下落
A line on the whereabouts
of Floyd Lawton.
死亡射手
Deadshot.
Lyla去俄罗斯是为了我
Lyla was in Russia for me,
Michaels特工对我有不可取代的价值
Agent Michaels is an asset
I can't easily replace.
我知道你也认为她是不可取代的
I know you find her
similarly irreplaceable.
把她带回来 Diggle
Bring her home,Mr.Diggle.
谢谢
Thanks.
好久没逮捕你了
It's been a while since I arrested you.
我都忘了那感觉多好了
I'd forgotten how good it feels.
我在为他做事
I was working for...him.
哪个他
Him who?
你在掩护的那个人
The guy who cost you your shield.
我和他是一伙的
I'm on his team.
你也是
You are,too.
似曾相识的感觉啊
Anybody else having serious deja vu?
没关系 我们正要放了他
That's all right,we're letting him go.
我们搞错了
Our mistake.
他只是在错误的时间
出现在了错误的地点
He was just in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
好吧 趁有人改变主意前
我们抓紧离开这里吧
Ok,uh,let's just get out of here
before anyone changes their mind.
打开这台机器可能导致的灾难性后果
The potentially catastrophic
risk of turning on this machine
远大于其可能带来的科学收获
far outweigh any scientific
gain that might come from it.
人们必须明白像这样的技术有多危险
The people need to understand just
how dangerous technology like this is.
以及其可能导致的灾难性事件
And the very real possibility
of a cataclysmic event.
你去哪儿了
Where'd you go?
没出什么事吧
Is everything ok?
没事
Yeah.
只是要请几天假处理一些私事
Just need a few personal days.
发生什么了
What's going on?
得去帮朋友一个忙
Have to help a friend.
哪个朋友
Who?
Lyla Michaels
Lyla Michaels.
他的特工女友
为超能力研究组工作
It's his spy girlfriend
that works for A.R.G.U.S.
她去了俄国找死亡射手 为了我
She went to Russia looking
for Deadshot, for me.
现在她失踪了
Now she's missing.
Felicity 我想是时候去莫斯科
看看Queen集团的子公司了
Felicity... I think it's time we visited
our Queen Consolidated subsidiary in Moscow.
没错
Yeah.
Oliver 你这是在干什么
Oliver,what are you doing?
只是帮朋友一个忙
Just need to help a friend.
我不能要求你这么做
I can't ask you to do that.
你没有要求我
You didn't.
- Sara
- 我叫Ivo
Sara... My name's Ivo.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
Tommy
Tommy.
那么
So.
你是如何到这座岛上的呢 Tommy
How did you come to be
on this island,Tommy?
我想不会是你自愿来的吧
I assume it wasn't by choice.
我的船遇到了海难
My,uh... Boat was shipwrecked here.
我是唯一的幸存者
And I was the only survivor.
很遗憾听到这个消息
Well,I'm sorry to hear that.
那你有没有探索过这座岛屿呢
Did you explore the island much?
一部分吧
Some of it.
为什么这么问
Why?
你不会刚好发现了一艘
日本皇家海军的潜艇吧 有没有
You didn't happen to run across a
Japanese Imperial Navy submarine,did you?
二战时 每个国家都在研究终极武器
During World War II, every country was
trying to develop the ultimate weapon.
美国有曼哈顿计划 不必多说
The United States had the
Manhattan Project,of course;
德国搞了"铀俱乐部"
the Nazis had das Uranverein.
至于日本人 他们开发了Mirakuru
And the Japanese,well,
they had Mirakuru.
干细胞和基因疗法 领先时代数十年
Stem cell and genetic therapies,
decades ahead of their time.
每次战争 都会促进科学进步
Every war advances the cause of science.
日本人发明了一种血清
可以增加力量
And the Japanese,they had developed a
serum that caused increased strength.
促进细胞再生
Rapid cell regeneration.
他们称之为Mirakuru
They called it Mirakuru.
"奇迹"
"Miracle.
他们以为能创造出一支
由超级战士组成的军团
" Thought they could create
an army of super soldiers.
他们用一艘潜艇运输唯一一批血清
They were transporting their
only supply via submarine
结果这艘潜艇遭到了盟军强大火力
when that sub came under heavy
fire by the allied forces.
在这片群岛触礁搁浅
And it ran aground in
this chain of islands.
多亏了你
我们现在能确定就是在这座岛屿
Thanks to you... We now
know it's this island.
是你杀了我的朋友们
You killed my friends.
也就是说只能靠你...
来帮我们找到那艘潜艇
Which means it's up to you...
To help us find that sub.
你是不是忘了点什么
Are you forgetting something?
你们这是要去哪里
Where do you think you're going?
塔希提岛
Tahiti.
有意思
That's funny.
飞行记录显示你们要去莫斯科
The flight manifest says
you're going to Moscow.
我们会顺路在那儿停一下
你懂的 在去塔希提岛后
Well,we're going to stop by
there, you know,after Tahiti.
什么样的合伙人会背着其他人去
我们的海外公司访问呢
What kind of partner decides to interact with
our overseas holdings behind the other one's back?
是我疏忽了
It was an oversight.
幸运的是 我这个合伙人收拾行李很快
Well,lucky for our
partnership, I'm a fast packer.
Oliver 她一路跟着可没什么好处
Oliver,her tagging along
does not help matters any.
我会看好她的
I will take care of her.
John
John.
我们会把Lyla带回来的
We're going to bring Lyla back.
不论她在哪儿
Wherever she is.
明天上午十点我安排了一个
I've arranged a meeting with
the chief operating officer
与莫斯科子公司运营总裁的会议
of our Moscow subsidiary
tomorrow at 10:00 a.m.
可别又错过了
Try your hardest not to miss this one.
我不是你想的那种人
You know,I'm not this person
that you seem to think I am.
- 那得看情况
- 什么情况
- That depends.
- On what?
比如当我发现你用集团的飞机跟
你的助手出去欢度周末的时候
On if I think you use the corporate jet
for a weekend of fun with your assistant.
你在说什么
Excuse me?
一个金发IT美女
A blonde I.T.girl all of a sudden
突然被提拔成CEO的助理
gets promoted to be
assistant to the C.E.O.?
只有两种可能
There are only two ways that happens.
一种情况是她是你的亲戚
但她明显不是
One is nepotism, and she
doesn't look like your cousin.
真的不是你想的那样
That...is... absolutely not happening.
那她到底有什么资历
What were her qualifications?
除了她那一条又一条的超短裙
Aside from an abundance of short skirts.
她的裙子也没那么 短
Her skirts aren't that...short.
你们说什么呢
What was that about?
没什么
Nothing.
Knyazev那边已经安排好了
Everything with Knyazev is set.
你还有俄罗斯黑手党的朋友
You have friends in the Russian mafia?
就当我一点都不惊讶好了
Color me at not at all surprised.
你直接打车去酒店吧
You're going straight
to the hotel in a cab.
不 你要抛下我一个人 跟她一起走吗
No,you're leaving me with her?
Dig和我得去喝一杯
Dig and I need to get a drink.
我不介意也喝一点儿啊
Well...I...wouldn't mind a drink.
Loring女士
Ms.Loring.
没想到你是会来夜店的人
Didn't take you for
the club-hopping type.
我来办正事
Well,I'm here on business.
我妈妈没事吧
Is everything ok with my mom?
正好 我们得谈谈这事
We need to discuss
something about this case.
你男朋友昨晚被警方拘捕了
Your boyfriend Roy was
arrested last night.
我知道 这事有点误会
I know,but it was actually
a misunderstanding.
他已经被释放了
He got released.
但是有些狗仔抓住你母亲不放
Well,a few reporters
got hold of the story
现在 你跟小混混交往的事
已经变成了他们的口舌
and they now know you're
dating a known felon.
Thea 你母亲的案子生死攸关
Thea,your mother is
on trial for her life.
她所有的辩护都建立在
Her whole defense pivots on
being seen as a loving mother
全心全意为你们俩考虑的基础上
who did what she had to
do to protect her children,
因为她是一位伟大的母亲
what kind of parent she was.
我们希望其他人看到的是两个
家教良好 正直的孩子
We need the people to know that she
raised you to make good decisions.
如果你还顾念你的母亲
就该立刻和对方分手
So if you care about your mom, you're going
to have to end this relationship immediately.
Oliver Queen
Oliver Queen?
我最喜欢的美国人
My favorite American!
Dabro pazhalavat
Dabro pazhalavat.
好久不见
It has been too long.
John Diggle 这位是Anatoly Knyazev
John Diggle,this is Anatoly Knyazev.
感谢你抽空见我们
Thank you for meeting us.
你有了Oliver作担保
就是仅次于Oliver的我最喜欢的美国人
If Oliver vouches for you, you're
my second favorite American.
先来干一杯
First,a toast.
我不喝酒 谢谢
None for me,thanks.
干杯
Prochnost.
强者更强
To strength.
现在可以谈正事了
Now.Business.
这个女的就是你要找的人吧
This is woman you look for,yes?
这相片是两天前在古拉格监狱拍下的
Picture is from two days
ago,from gulag-- prison.
Lyla被抓了
Lyla was arrested?
不尽然
Not quite.
据我所知 她是试图闯进监狱
From what I hear,she
was trying to break in.
为什么
Why?
我不知道
I do not know.
可惜她出不来了
But clearly she had
issues breaking back out.
古拉格 俄国最恐怖的监狱
Gulag,worst in Russia.
被称为Koshmar
It's called Koshmar.
噩梦
The nightmare.
里面有各种各样心理变态的暴力分子
还有杀人犯
It's full of violent
psychopaths and killers.
这些还都只是看守
And that's just the guards.
Anatoly 我们得进去把她救出来
Anatoly,we need a way into
the gulag to extract her.
还没等你出来 就挨枪子了
You get in,you get
shot before you get out.
或者干脆出不来了
Or end up like your friend.
你救不了她
Mmm,it's impossible.
不把她救出来 我绝不会离开俄罗斯
The only thing that's impossible is us
leaving this country without this woman.
挺对我胃口
I like this guy.
在俄罗斯 没有"乐观"这个词
We have no word for
"optimist" in Russian.
想进古拉格
唯一的办法就是成为那里的犯人
The only way in to
Koshmar is as prisoner.
里面有个看守欠我个人情
Now,I have guard there,owes me favor.
我们可以找他
It could work.
但是你只有5%的可能会成功
I'll give you one shot in twenty.
- 你安排吧 我进去
- 不
- Set it up.I'll go.
- No.
- 让我去
- 不
- It has to be me.
- No.
Oliver 你不能有事
Oliver,what if something
happens to you in there?
如果是我 Felicity 或者Isabel出事
What happens to me,Felicity,or
Isabel,for that matter?
你还可以在外面接应我们
You have to be on the
outside making the moves.
让我去 我没问题的
I'll go inside.I've got this.
带的有点多啊
Now that is a lot of drugs.
是Knyazev友情赞助的
Courtesy of Knyazev.
足够让我蹲古拉格了
About enough weight to
land me in the Koshmar.
你得穿上这个
You need to be wearing
this when they process you.
好让看守把它没收
Guards will take
it,but that's the point.
这位 就是Knyazev在监狱里的朋友
This... Is Knyazev's
man inside the prison.
那个看守
A guard.
他知道Lyla关在哪里
He'll know where in the
gulag Lyla is being held.
得手之后 你和Lyla
得去约定的地方找我们 否则...
When all hell breaks loose, you need to meet
us at the rendezvous point with Lyla,or...
我就得永远留在俄国了
Or I am a permanent Russian.
我多嘴一句...
这就是我们的最佳方案了
Just thinking out loud... But,are we sure
this is the best plan we can come up with?
- 我知道Lyla是你的朋友 但是...
- Felicity Lyla不是我的朋友
I know Lyla's your friend,but...
Felicity,Lyla isn't my friend.
她是我的前妻
She was my wife.
能解释一下吗
Explain that sentence.
Lyla和我在阿富汗军中相识
Lyla and I met in the
army back in Afghanistan.
但是回国后
我们的婚姻并没能维系下去
But we didn't stay married
long once we got stateside.
想来是因为没仗可打了
也就不会过日子了
Couldn't figure out a way to stay
married without a war to fight.
后来她加入了警卫队
So she joined A.R.G.U.S.
而我第三次踏上了征途
and I circled back for my third tour.
我一定要带她回去 Felicity
I can't leave here without her,Felicity.
一定
Just can't.
还有两分钟
Two minute warning.
祝你好运 John
Good luck,John.
他进去了
They have him.
行动开始
Clock's running.
Zhivey zhivey
Zhivey,zhivey.
快点
Hurry up.
外套不错
Khoroshaya kurtka.
你犯了什么事
What,uh,crime fits your punishment?
毒品 你呢?
Drugs.And you?
我发表了公开演说
I gave speech.
揭露政府的腐败行为
About government corruption.
不意外
Right.
我们这像你这样的人可不多
It is rare to see one of
your people in Koshmar.
什么人 美国人
What,American?
黑人
Chernokozhiy.
黑人在这不太受欢迎
Ehh... Chernokozhiy not popular here.
好怕怕呀
Shocker.
Dig不会有事的吧
You think Dig's ok?
我想他跟五分钟前你问我时一样没问题
I think he's doing the same as he was
when you asked me five minutes ago.
他们来了
They're coming.
就是他们把俄国警车便宜卖给我们
They sell us Russian
police truck for cheap.
这是你要的东西
Vot mashina,kotoraya vam nuzhna.
这是一百五十万
Sto pyatisot tysyach rubley.
跪下
Na koleni.
不给我就杀了你全家
Yesli vy sde syete eto, moi lyudi
vas, I vashi deti osanutsya sirotami.
你跟他说了什么
What'd you say?
求他
Please.
知道吗 在俄国有个集中营
You know,in Russia,there is gulag.
几乎跟这儿一样糟
Almost as bad as this.
- Sara
- 别叫名字
Sara-- Don't
say my name.
被他们发现我们认识 我们都会被杀的
If they find out we know each
other,they'll kill us both.
我以为你淹死了
I thought you drowned.
当我醒来时 船已经不见了
When I came up,the boat was gone.
我以为你也淹死了
And I thought you were,too.
我在海上漂了几天后
这艘船...他们发现了我
And I was floating out there for
days when this ship... They found me.
然后救了我
And they saved me.
所以你帮他们做事
Is that why you're helping them?
我别无选择
I don't have a choice.
我得去警告我的朋友们
I need to warn my friends.
你不是说他们死了
You said they were dead.
他们可没那么容易就死了
They're not that easy to kill.
别乱动
Try not to move.
这东西闻着真恶心
It smells like puke!
这对伤口有好处
It'll heal your wounds.
你必须走
You have to go.
离开这儿
Get out of here.
去高点的地方
Get to higher ground.
我不会离开你的
I'm not leaving you.
我不能拖累你
I will not be the reason
something happens to you.
那就没什么问题了
Then we're in agreement.
这是我自己的选择
Because I make my own choices.
你是个坚强的女人
You are a strong woman.
我会为我关心的人做任何事
When I care about someone,there's
nothing I won't do for them.
我们又有个...共同点了
Another thing... we have in common.
烧伤降低了你的体温
The burns,they're lowering
your body temperature.
过来
Here.
你整晚都去哪儿了
Where you been all night?
干活
Working.
你该好好歇歇
Well,you deserve a break.
其实 我想了想
Um,actually,I've been thinking.
或许我们该给彼此多点空间
Maybe we should take some space.
我是说我们朝夕相处
I mean,we work together
and live together.
都快窒息了
It's kind of getting hard to breathe.
什么时候开始这么觉得的
Since when?
等等 这跟那个蹦出来的女律师有关系吗
Oh,wait,does this have to with
that lawyer lady dropping by?
不 这跟你上个月
No,this has to do with the fact
被逮捕的就有两次有关
that you've been arrested
twice in the last month.
别这样 我已经尽量避免惹麻烦了
Come on. I've been trying
to stay out of trouble.
这几周我连个擦伤都没有
My body hasn't had a
scratch on it in weeks.
我是说除了你抓的那几道
Well,I mean,excluding the
ones that you put there.
那天晚上呢
And the other night?
那是个误会
Was a misunderstanding.
Roy...我做不来
Roy... This just isn't working,ok?
实在办不到
Not for me.
Thea 你不是那个意思对吗
Thea,you can't mean that.
我就是那个意思 对不起
I do. I'm sorry.
那些人... 他们很好斗
Those men... They are Vory.
而且很有势力
They are in charge.
最好离他们远点
It's best to stay away.
Got it.
Listen,I'm looking for a
guard named Sergei Pavelski.
在那边角落那儿
了解
我在找一个叫Sergei Pavelski的看守
美国佬... 现在起你是我的玩物
American... You are suka now.
真的要这么做吗
Are we seriously going to do this?
我想是的
Guess so.
严禁打架
Fighting strictly prohibited.
请给我杯伏特加
Vodki,pozhaluysta.
你错过演出了
You missed the tour.
发生了什么事
What happened to you?
我看到了一辆我以前有过的俄国车
I saw a Russian vehicle
that I simply had to have.
这是你来俄国的目的吗
Is that why you came to Russia?
买车
Car shopping?
我只点了一杯
Oh,I just ordered one.
这杯是我的 再来一杯
One's for me.
这是个冷藏室
This cold room.
你要在这儿待6个小时
Six hours for you.
6个小时 你不能关我这么久
Six hours? You can't
keep me in here that long.
那就7小时
Now seven hours.
你那么做太傻了...而且
Well,that was pretty
stupid... Then again,
你确实也不是什么聪明人
you never really were
one of the brightest guys.
死亡射手
Deadshot.
你脊柱冻透了没
Your spine frozen through yet?
相信我
Trust me.
这点冷才不是我现在的最大问题
My problem here isn't with the cold.
什么 你还没原谅我杀了你哥哥吗
What,you still haven't forgiven
me for shooting your brother?
伙计 你还真记仇
Man,you really hold a grudge.
我知道你来这儿干嘛
I know why you're here.
那个女孩
That girl.
来自警卫队的
From A.R.G.U.S.
看来Lyla不止找到了关于你的线索
Lyla didn't find a lead on you.
而且找到了你
She found you.
- 大家真的认为我跟Felicity是...
- 没有
- Does everyone really think that Felicity and I are...
- No.
只是在Queen集团工作的人都这么认为
Just everyone who works
at Queen Consolidated.
我跟她只是朋友
She's just a friend.
你看着不像有女性朋友的人
You don't seem like the kind
of man who has female friends.
我能问你个私人问题吗
Can I ask you a personal question?
喝了几杯伏特加 我或许会回答吧
With some vodka in
me,I just might answer.
为什么救我家族的公司对你那么重要
Why does saving my family's
company mean so much to you?
女强人Sheryl Sandberg不会那么说的...
Despite what Sheryl
Sandberg might say...
但女人在商场打拼还是不容易
It still isn't that easy to
make it as a woman in business.
我...放弃了很多东西
I've...given up a lot.
如果我不能成功 那有何意义
Which means if I don't succeed at
everything, then what was the point?
我能问你一个私人问题吗
May I ask you a personal question?
其他人问过 但问了也白问
Others have tried and failed.
你为何这么想
让我认为你是个懒惰的白痴
Why do you try so hard to make
me think that you're a lazy idiot?
我知道你不是
I know you're not.
在你的伪装下 我能清楚地看到
Underneath that swagger,I
see you pretty clearly.
是吗
Really?
你看到什么了
And what do you see?
你很聪明
You're intelligent.
有紧迫感
Driven.
还很孤独
And lonely.
你怎么看出来的
How do you see that?
因为我也是那样的人
Because it's what I see
when I look in the mirror.
我们时间不多了
We don't have much time.
- 走吧
- 走 走了
- There you go.
- Let's go,let's go.
很高兴见到你 John
Nice seeing you,John.
请问还需要点别的吗
Can ***
我想不该再喝了
I ***
你会说俄语
You speak Russian.
只跟我朋友说
ONLY ***
直到九岁前 我都生长在莫斯科
I was raised in Moscow until I was nine.
然后一个家庭把我收养到美国
And then adopted by a family
that took me to America.
我花了几年时间才改掉口音
Took me years to get rid of my accent.
俄国口音在小学交朋友可不容易
It isn't easy making friends in grade
school when you sound like Natasha.
听起来你长久以来都很孤独
Sou ***
买单吧
Pay ***
我...没有太多时间
I...Don't have a lot of time.
我会很快的
I'll be quick.
五分钟 必须快点
Five minutes.Must hurry.
等这事搞定了 记得提醒我给你买包烟
Remind me to get you a pack of
cigarettes when this is all over.
我不抽烟的
I don't smoke.
你不会不带上我走吧
You weren't going to
leave without me,were you?
我真该马上杀了你
I should kill you right now!
你不会的
You won't.
为什么
Why?
因为只有我知道你女朋友关在哪里
BecauseI'm the only one who knows
where your little girlfriend is.
你可不傻
You're not stupid.
你没有逃离计划怎么会被关进来
You wouldn't put yourself in
here without an exit strategy.
我带你去找她...你带我出去
I take you to the
girl... You take me out.
Isabel 我得走了
Isabel,I have to go.
抱歉
Sorry.
我像是那种矫情的人吗
Do I strike you as someone
who needs to cuddle?
时候到了 准备好了吗
- Hi. - Hi. -
It's time.Ready?
- 是的 我...
- 我想她今晚可以休息了
Yeah,I-- I think she
can take the night off.
是吗
Don't you?
- Felicity...
- 发生在俄国的事过了就过了
Felicity... It--what happens
in Russia stays in Russia.
尽管没什么意义
Even when it makes no sense whatsoever.
我看 枪还是你拿好了
Guessin',uh,you want to hold on to that.
这边
This way.
你在想什么啊
What were you thinking?
什么
What?
俄国有超过六千四百万
到了法定年龄的女人
你却跟她上床
Over 64 million women over the age of
consent in Russia and you sleep with her.
不是说"发生在俄国的事过去就过去了"吗
So we're not doing the "What
happens in Russia stays in Russia?
我们还在俄国
" We're still in Russia.
在这个国家没有钱是办不到的事
There is nothing money
cannot buy in this country.
Diggle两分钟内会带Lyla出来
Diggle should be heading
out Lyla in two minutes.
越狱可不容易
Well,breaking out of prison
is harder than it looks.
你们应该都知道吧
You of all people should know that.
别出声 跟我来
Stay quiet. Follow me.
你会记得我们的吧...是吗
You'll remember the rest of us... Yes?
我保证
I promise.
我会回来的
I'll come back.
快走
Come on.
- 我们要游过去吗
- 不
- Are we making a swim for it?
- No.
我们一下水他们就会开枪的
They'd shoot us the
second we hit the water.
你说你朋友 他们有一台船用收音机 对吗
You said your friends,they have one
of the radios from the ship,right?
是的
Yeah.
看来你很会用嘛
You look like you know
what you're doing there.
过去几年 我学了许多意想不到的东西
In the past year,I've learned a
lot of things I never expected to.
我们都是
You and me both.
他们没听到你的声音是不会回应的
They won't respond unless
they hear your voice.
Shado
Shado.
你能听到我吗
ni neng ting dao wo ma
Slade
Slade.
你能听到我吗
Can you hear me?
谢天谢地 你还活着
Thank God you're alive.
- 是的 我在货船上...
- Sara 你在干嘛
Yeah,I'm on the freighter--
Sara,what are you doing?
他们只有两个人
There's only two of them.
他们还没离开迫击炮的攻击范围
They haven't moved from the
location of the mortar attack.
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
你刚确认你的朋友还活着
You just confirmed that
your friends are alive.
这意味着他们还是个威胁
Which means they're still a threat.
在我们杀掉他们之前
You know,until we kill them.
你个狗娘养的
You son of
a bitch--oh!
如果我说她在里面
你要怎样才不会朝我开枪
If I say she's in there, what's
keeping you from shooting me?
信誉
Honor.
你也该试一试讲信誉
You should try it some time.
Lyla
Lyla!
Johnny
Johnny?
准备回家吧
Ready to go home?
你来救我了
You came for me.
我一直会 以后也会
I always have. Always will.
死亡射手在这呢
Deadshot's here.
- 就在这监狱里
- 我知道
- In the prison.
- I know.
你打算怎么逃出去
What's your extraction plan?
随机应变吧
Depends.
现在几点
What time is it?
我穿着帅吧
YOU ***
走 我们走 快 快
Let's go,go,go,move,move,move!
这边
This way.
搞定 我切断了通信
Got it. I shut down the phones.
狱警们没法呼救了
The guards can't call for help.
你朋友和那女的到现在还没出现
他们出不来了
Your friend and that woman are not here
by now, they will not be here at all.
这下好多了
Much better.
都给我趴下
on***
Oliver 蹲下
Oliver,get down!
跟我来
Follow me!
快
Move!
我们逃出来了
We're clear.
停车
Stop the truck.
下车 快下车
Get out. Get out!
快点
Move.
这是信誉问题 John
That's the thing about honor,John.
你不会出尔反尔的
You can't turn it on and off.
我只是好奇
I'm just curious.
你知道你哥怎么死的吗
How is it you think your
brother ended up dead?
你要杀一个Andy保护的客户
结果你失手了
You shot a client that Andy
was protecting, and you missed.
我从未失手
I don't miss.
你哥才是目标人物
Your brother was the contract.
谁想杀Andy
Who would want to kill Andy?
不清楚 只知道一个化名
I don't know the names,just an alias.
Hive
Hive.
好好想吧 John
Food for thought,John.
够你想想的
Food for thought.
我们不聊聊昨晚的事吗
Are we going to discuss
what happened last night?
为什么呢
Why would we?
不为什么
No reason.
明天公司见
I'll see you in the office tomorrow.
多谢
Thank you.
你那么支持我
You had my back.
所以现在你知道那是什么感觉了吧
And now you know what it feels like.
你在这干什么
Wh--what are you--
what are you doing here?
问得好
Good question.
我接过很多从监狱打来的电话
I've gotten a lot of calls from prison,
但还没接到过我女友老妈打来的
but never from my girlfriend's mother.
我突然想起来
It occurred to me
我一直没机会认识你生命中最重要的男人
that I've never been given the
opportunity to meet the man in your life.
我不知道你女儿是否说过
她把我甩了
I don't know if she told you, but
your daughter kind of dumped me.
你要知道她是因为我才这样做的
And what you should know
is that she did it for me.
Jean跟我讲她找过你
Jean told me she came to see you.
我告诉她不该那么做
I told her she shouldn't have.
你为什么不跟我说实话呢
Why didn't you just tell me the truth?
咱们在一起 会对妈的案子不利
Us being together...
It can hurt her case.
Thea 你的社交生活
并不是影响我审判结果的决定因素
Thea... Your social life is not going
to be the determining factor in my trial.
乖女儿 你去年所经历的事情
Sweetheart,what you've had
to endure this last year
比多数人两辈子经历的还多
is more than most people
go through in two lifetimes.
但你不仅挺过来了 还有所成长
But you've not only
survived,you've flourished.
我想这跟Roy有很大关系
I think a lot of that
has to do with Roy.
所以作为你的母亲 我不允许你们分手
So,as your mother,I
forbid you not to see him.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不得不承认
这次俄国之行的结果不是我所预料的
I have to admit, this is not how I
anticipated my trip to Russia ending.
我只是庆幸我们能活着离开那里
I just feel lucky we made
it out of there alive.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不仅因为你来救我
Not just for coming for me.
还有你当时的选择
For doing what you had to once you did.
你是说跟死亡射手的合作么
You mean working with Deadshot.
你知道么 我跟Carly分手
是因为我不能在爱她的同时
You know,me and Carly broke
up because I couldn't love her
又恨着他
and hate him at the same time.
很荣幸我是个例外
I'm honored to be the exception.
Lyla 你永远是个例外
Lyla,you're always the exception.
不 不 让Waller去做吧
No,no,let Waller stew.
你留下吃早餐
Stay for breakfast.
除非你做拿手的蓝莓饼
Throw in your blueberry pancakes
我可能会考虑留下来
and you may be able to convince me.
帮忙把这个送到Isabel的办公室
Can you deliver this to
Isabel's office,please?
为什么选择她
Why her?
我是说 除了她有长腿模特的身材
I mean,besides the...
obvious leggy model reason.
顺其自然而已
It just kind of happened.
并不代表什么
It didn't mean anything.
因为我的生活
Because of the life that I lead...
我觉得最好还是不要...
I just think that it's better to not...
和我真正在乎的人在一起
Be with someone that I
could really care about.
好吧 我觉得你值得比她更好的人
Well,I think... I think
you deserve better than her.
找到他们的位置了
We have their location.
他对我们而言不再有用了
This one's no longer of use to us.
让我们看看你能有多大本事
可以取出你脑袋里的子弹
Let's see how good you are... At
removing a bullet from your head.
等等
Wait!
他或许还有用处
He could still be useful.
她说得对
She's right.
一旦我们干掉他那俩朋友
我们还需要他带我们去到那个墓穴
Once we get rid of his friends, we'll
need him to lead us to the graves.
有时候我在想这里谁是老大
Sometimes I wonder who
gives the orders here.
是你... 还是你的小跟班
You... or your little bouzin.
你又要回岛上了
You're going back to the island.
Oliver
Oliver.
--------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly
Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 禾希饭 DB CXRR 金万藏 佐佐木 Crystal
校对: Andrea∞Quinn
时间轴:YTET-pluto无肉筋 可可与可心
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-pluto无肉筋 可可与可心
绿箭侠
第二季 第六集 完
Arrow
Season 2 Episode 6